<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Fighter Rank Compose</string>
    <string name="title">Fighter Rank</string>
    <string name="app_icon_description">Fighter Rank Icon</string>
    <string name="fighter_image">fighter image</string>
    <string name="fighter_record">Fighter Record (W-D-L)</string>
    <string name="wins_by_knockout">Wins By\nKnockout</string>
    <string name="wins_by_submission">Wins By\nSubmission</string>
    <string name="division">division</string>
    <string name="striking_accuracy">Striking Accuracy</string>
    <string name="takedown_accuracy">Takedown Accuracy</string>
    <string name="fighter_not_found">Fighter not found!</string>
    <string name="failed_to_load_fighters">Failed to load fighters!</string>
    <string name="about_icon">About Icon</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="source_code">Source Code Icon</string>
    <string name="masdika_ilhan_mansiz">Masdika Ilhan Mansiz</string>

    <!--DATA-->
    <string-array name="fighter_names">
        <item>Masdika Ilhan Mansiz</item>
        <item>Ilia Topuria</item>
        <item>Islam Makhachev</item>
        <item>Merab Dvalishvili</item>
        <item>Khamzat Chimaev</item>
        <item>Alexandre Pantoja</item>
        <item>Alex Pereira</item>
        <item>Alexander Volkanovski</item>
        <item>Jack Della Maddalena</item>
        <item>Tom Aspinall</item>
        <item>Dricus Du Plessis</item>
        <item>Max Holloway</item>
        <item>Magomed Ankalaev</item>
        <item>Belal Muhammad</item>
        <item>Arman Tsarukyan</item>
        <item>Charles Oliveira</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighter_divisions">
        <item>Lightweight</item>
        <item>Lightweight</item>
        <item>Welterweight</item>
        <item>Bantamweight</item>
        <item>Middleweight</item>
        <item>Flyweight</item>
        <item>Light Heavyweight</item>
        <item>Featherweight</item>
        <item>Welterweight</item>
        <item>Heavyweight</item>
        <item>Middleweight</item>
        <item>Lightweight</item>
        <item>Light Heavyweight</item>
        <item>Welterweight</item>
        <item>Lightweight</item>
        <item>Lightweight</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighter_titles">
        <item>El Macho</item>
        <item>El Matador</item>
        <item />
        <item>The Machine</item>
        <item>Borz</item>
        <item>The Cannibal</item>
        <item>Poatan</item>
        <item>The Great</item>
        <item />
        <item />
        <item>Stillknocks</item>
        <item>Blessed</item>
        <item />
        <item>Remember The Name</item>
        <item>Ahalkalakets</item>
        <item>Do Bronxs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighter_images" tools:ignore="TypographyDashes">
        <item>https://i.postimg.cc/h4zmMmj0/Untitled-design-11.png</item>
        <item>https://www.ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2024-10/TOPURIA_ILIA_L_BELT_10-26.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-11/MAKHACHEV_ISLAM_L_10-22.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-10/DVALISHVILI_MERAB_L_BELT_10-04.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-08/CHIMAEV_KHAMZAT_L_BELTMOCK.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-06/PANTOJA_ALEXANDRE_L_BELT_06-28.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-03/PEREIRA_ALEX_L_BELT_03-08.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2024-02/VOLKANOVSKI_ALEXANDER_L_BELT_02-17.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-05/DELLA_MADDALENA_JACK_L_BELTMOCK.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-10/ASPINALL_TOM_L_BELT_10-25.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-08/DU_PLESSIS_DRICUS_L_01-20.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-07/HOLLOWAY_MAX_L_BMF_BELT_07-19.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2024-10/ANKALAEV_MAGOMED_L_10-26.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2023-05/MUHAMMAD_BELAL_L_05-06.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-01/TSARUKYAN_ARMAN_L_01-18.png</item>
        <item>https://ufc.com/images/styles/athlete_bio_full_body/s3/2025-10/OLIVEIRA_CHARLES_L_10-11.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighter_descriptions">
        <item>Masdika Ilhan Mansiz is widely considered the greatest anomaly in the history of combat sports, a fighter whose record reads more like a video game glich than a human achievement. Born in Jakarta, Indonesia, on August 17, 1998, to a Turkish father and an Indonesian mother, Mansiz was a prodigy who began training in Pencak Silat and traditional oil wrestling before he could read. His journey did not follow the traditional path; he spent over a decade competing in unsanctioned bouts across Southeast Asia and Europe, building a mythical reputation in the underground circuit before ever stepping foot in a major cage. By the time he signed with the UFC, whispers of a \"ghost\" with a perfect record had already terrified the division, but no one was prepared for the violence he was about to unleash upon the lightweight elite.\n\nInside the octagon, Mansiz operates under the terrifying moniker \"El Macho\", a nickname that perfectly encapsulates his aura of supreme dominance and raw masculinity. His fighting style is an unsolvable riddle, blending the erratic, bone–breaking striking of Silat with impeccable boxing fundamentals. However, his defining trait is his touch of death; he possesses the kind of one–punch power that simply shouldn\'t exist in the 155–pound division. With a staggering 49 knockouts on his résumé, he rarely engages in tactical chess matches. Instead, he stalks his prey with a high guard, walking through fire to land the single blow that disconnects his opponent from consciousness. He fights with a cold, predatory silence, never trash–talking, yet his presence alone causes opponents to freeze.\n\nHis ascent through the UFC ranks was the most violent in promotional history. While most prospects take years to climb the ladder, Mansiz cleared the top 15 in record time, often fighting twice in one month because he sustained zero damage in his bouts. His 54–0–0 professional record is unprecedented, surpassing legends like Khabib Nurmagomedov and Floyd Mayweather combined in terms of sheer volume and finishing rate. Critics initially claimed his record was padded, but he silenced them by knocking out three former champions in the first round consecutively. His grappling, often untested due to his quick finishes, was revealed to be elite when he secured three rare submission victories against high–level black belts who foolishly tried to take him down to avoid his hands.\n\nThe crowning achievement of his career occurred at UFC 320 in a historic stadium show in Jakarta. Mansiz faced the reigning champion in a unification bout that was billed as \"The Irresistible Force vs. The Immovable Object.\" The fight lasted less than two rounds. After systematically breaking down the champion\'s legs with devastating kicks, Mansiz slipped a jab and landed a thunderous spinning back elbow—a technique from his Silat roots—that instantly ended the fight. The knockout was heard throughout the arena, cementing his status not just as the UFC Lightweight Champion, but as a cultural icon who brought the world of MMA to its knees.\n\nAs of late 2025, Masdika Ilhan Mansiz sits on a throne of his own creation, boasting an immaculate 54–0–0 record. The statistics are mind-bending: 49 knockouts, 3 submissions, and only two fights in his entire life that have gone to the judges\' scorecards. He has effectively cleared out two generations of lightweights, leaving the UFC matchmakers in a desperate search for anyone brave enough to sign a contract against him. \"El Macho\" is no longer just a fighter; he is viewed as a mythological figure, a living god of war whose legacy is etched in history as the most destructive force the sport has ever seen.</item>
        <item>Ilia Topuria represents a new generation of mixed martial artists, blending immense technical skill with unshakable self–belief. Born in Halle Westfalen, Germany, on January 21, 1997, to Georgian parents, Topuria\’s early life was defined by movement. His family moved to Georgia when he was seven, where he began his martial arts journey with Greco–Roman wrestling. At the age of 15, his family relocated again, this time settling in Alicante, Spain. It was here, at the Climent Club, that he discovered Brazilian Jiu–Jitsu and mixed martial arts, honing the skills that would eventually make him one of the most dangerous fighters on the planet. He proudly represents both Georgia and Spain, carrying the flags of both nations on his path to glory.\n\nKnown by the nickname "El Matador", Topuria’s fighting style is a masterful combination of brutal efficiency and technical prowess. While he possesses some of the crispest and most powerful boxing in the sport, often attacking the body to set up devastating headshots, his foundation is in elite grappling. Alongside his brother, Aleksandre, Ilia became one of the first Georgian black belts in Brazilian Jiu–Jitsu, and this expertise is evident in his suffocating ground game. He is not just a striker who can grapple, or a grappler who can strike; he is a complete and seamless martial artist, capable of ending a fight by knockout or submission with equal confidence from any position.\n\nHis professional career began in 2015, and he quickly amassed an undefeated record in European promotions, including MFE and Brave Combat Federation, finishing nearly every opponent he faced. Topuria entered the UFC in 2020 with significant hype, which he immediately justified. He began a relentless climb up the featherweight ranks, showcasing his diverse skill set in a series of dominant victories. He displayed his knockout power against striking specialists like Jai Herbert and Ryan Hall, and demonstrated his grappling superiority by submitting BJJ black belt Bryce Mitchell with a suffocating arm–triangle choke, earning multiple "Performance of the Night" bonuses along the way.\n\nThe defining moment of his career arrived at UFC 298 in February 2024. Topuria faced the long–reigning and dominant featherweight king, Alexander Volkanovski. Despite Volkanovski’s legendary status, Topuria remained supremely confident, predicting a knockout. He delivered on that promise in the second round, cornering the champion against the fence and landing a perfect right hook that ended Volkanovski’s historic reign and crowned "El Matador" the new undisputed UFC Featherweight Champion. This victory solidified his status as a true superstar and the first–ever champion representing Georgia in the UFC.\n\nFollowing his championship win, Topuria’s star has only continued to rise, culminating in a historic 2024 and 2025. He successfully defended his featherweight title in October 2024, securing another spectacular knockout against former champion Max Holloway at UFC 308. Not content with dominating one division, Topuria then moved up to the lightweight division. In June 2025, at UFC 317, he faced Charles Oliveira for the vacant 155–pound title. Once again, Topuria showcased his devastating power, knocking out the submission specialist in the first round to become a two–division UFC champion. As of late 2025, he holds an immaculate 17–0 professional record and is widely regarded as the number one pound-for-pound fighter in the world.</item>
        <item>Islam Makhachev stands as the undisputed torchbearer of the formidable Dagestani fighting dynasty, representing the culmination of Abdulmanap Nurmagomedov’s lifelong vision for mixed martial arts dominance. Born in Makhachkala, Russia, Makhachev grew up in the rugged mountains of Dagestan, where combat sports are a way of life. From a young age, he trained alongside his close friend and future legend, Khabib Nurmagomedov, under the strict tutelage of Khabib’s father. This environment forged a discipline and mental toughness that would eventually separate him from his peers. Before making waves in professional MMA, Makhachev proved his grappling supremacy by becoming a Combat Sambo World Champion, laying the groundwork for a style that seamlessly blends suffocating wrestling with technical precision.\n\nWhile often compared to his mentor and teammate Khabib, Makhachev brings a distinct and evolved approach to the octagon. His fighting style is a masterful integration of elite sambo, judo, and increasingly dangerous striking. Unlike the relentless, chaotic mauling often associated with the Dagestani style, Makhachev operates with surgical patience and efficiency. He utilizes highly technical trips and sweeps to bring opponents to the canvas, where he applies crushing top pressure. Furthermore, he has developed a sophisticated stand-up game, possessing one of the best defensive strike rates in UFC history and a deceptive knockout power that forces opponents to respect him on the feet as much as on the ground.\n\nMakhachev\'s journey in the UFC began in 2015, and although he showed immediate promise, his path to the title was a marathon rather than a sprint. Early in his tenure, he suffered a shock knockout loss to Adriano Martins, a setback that served as a crucial lesson in caution and defense. Following that lone defeat, Makhachev embarked on a remarkably dominant winning streak, methodically dismantling contenders and rendering high-level opponents helpless. For years, he was considered the \"uncrowned king\" of the lightweight division, often avoided by top-ranked fighters due to the immense risk he posed to their title aspirations.\n\nThe culmination of his life\'s work arrived at UFC 280 in October 2022, when he faced the record-breaking submission artist Charles Oliveira for the vacant lightweight championship. In a performance that silenced all doubters, Makhachev outstruck the Brazilian on the feet before submitting him with an arm-triangle choke in the second round. This victory not only secured the gold but also fulfilled the prophecy of his late coach, Abdulmanap, returning the lightweight belt to Dagestan. It was a moment of immense emotional weight, signaling that the student had finally stepped out of the shadow of his predecessors to forge his own legacy.\n\nSince capturing the throne, Makhachev has solidified his status as the best fighter in the world through a series of historic title defenses. He engaged in a defining rivalry with featherweight great Alexander Volkanovski, defeating him twice; first by a grueling unanimous decision that tested his resolve, and subsequently with a stunning first-round head-kick knockout that showcased his evolved striking arsenal. Most recently, in June 2024 at UFC 302, he defended his belt against fan-favorite Dustin Poirier. Despite facing adversity and a deep cut, Makhachev showcased his champion\'s heart, securing a submission victory in the fifth round. These performances have firmly entrenched him at the top of the pound-for-pound rankings, proving that he is not just a grappler, but a complete martial artist dominating the sport\'s deepest division</item>
        <item>Merab Dvalishvili is the personification of relentless perseverance and unbreakable will. Born in Tbilisi, Georgia, on January 10, 1991, his journey to the pinnacle of mixed martial arts was paved with hardship. Like many of his compatriots, he grew up wrestling in the traditional Georgian style, chidaoba, before transitioning to sambo and eventually judo. Seeking a better life and a path to professional fighting, Dvalishvili immigrated to the United States at the age of 21. His early years in America were grueling; he worked labor-intensive construction jobs to survive while training at night, often sleeping in gyms or cramped shared spaces. This difficult beginning forged a work ethic that is unmatched in the sport, earning him the fitting nickname \"The Machine.\"\n\nHis fighting style is a unique phenomenon in the world of combat sports, defined not by one-punch knockout power, but by weaponized cardio and overwhelming pressure. Dvalishvili does not just fight his opponents; he drowns them. He possesses an seemingly infinite gas tank that allows him to chain wrestle, strike, and scramble at a frantic pace from the first second to the last. While many fighters slow down as the rounds progress, Dvalishvili seems to get stronger, breaking his opponents mentally as they realize he will not stop coming forward. He holds the record for the most takedown attempts in a single UFC bout, a testament to a strategy that relies on sheer volume and an inability to accept fatigue.\n\nDvalishvili’s UFC career had a rocky start, beginning with two consecutive losses that might have discouraged a lesser man. However, he rebounded with a ferocity that stunned the division, embarking on one of the longest winning streaks in bantamweight history. His path to the title was complicated by his profound loyalty to his close friend and training partner, Aljamain Sterling, who held the belt at the time. Dvalishvili famously refused to fight his \"brother\" for the championship, choosing to act as a gatekeeper and clearing out other contenders while waiting for his turn. This act of loyalty delayed his own glory but earned him immense respect within the MMA community.\n\nTo earn his title shot, Dvalishvili had to run a gauntlet of legends, defeating three former UFC champions in consecutive bouts. He first retired the legendary Jose Aldo by neutralizing the Brazilian\'s striking with suffocating clinches. He then completely dominated the feared striker and former champion Petr Yan, attempting a record-breaking 49 takedowns and winning every second of the fight. He followed this by defeating Olympic gold medalist and former two-division champion Henry Cejudo at UFC 298. In that fight, Dvalishvili not only out-wrestled the Olympian but also famously picked him up and carried him across the octagon while conversing with Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg, displaying a terrifying level of comfort and dominance.\n\nThe culmination of his incredible journey arrived in September 2024 at UFC 306, held at the Sphere in Las Vegas. Facing the superstar striker and reigning champion Sean O\'Malley, Dvalishvili executed a flawless game plan. He disregarded O\'Malley\'s dangerous feints and sniping ability, relentlessly taking the champion down and mauling him on the ground for five rounds. He won a decisive unanimous decision to become the undisputed UFC Bantamweight Champion. With this victory, Dvalishvili not only completed his transformation from a struggling immigrant construction worker to the king of the world, but he also solidified Georgia\'s golden era in MMA alongside his compatriot Ilia Topuria.</item>
        <item>Khamzat Chimaev represents one of the most terrifying and enigmatic forces to ever enter the Ultimate Fighting Championship. Born in the war-torn republic of Chechnya, Russia, on May 1, 1994, his early life was forged in conflict and resilience. Like many from his region, he found an outlet in freestyle wrestling, winning a bronze medal at the Russian Junior National Championships before immigrating to Sweden at the age of 18. In Sweden, his wrestling dominance continued as he won multiple national championships without surrendering a single point. He eventually found his way to the Allstars Training Center in Stockholm, where he transitioned to mixed martial arts, quickly gaining a reputation in the gym as a ferocious talent who overwhelmed even seasoned veterans.\n\nKnown by the moniker \"Borz\", which means \"The Wolf\" in Chechen, Chimaev possesses a fighting style that is primal yet highly technical. He is an aggressive wrestler who does not merely look to control opponents but seeks to physically break them. His grappling is suffocating, often carrying opponents across the cage and slamming them to the canvas with ease. However, unlike many grappling-heavy fighters, Chimaev possesses legitimate one-punch knockout power in his hands. This dual threat creates a sense of inevitable doom for his adversaries; they fear the takedown so much that they become susceptible to his striking, or they overcommit to striking and find themselves instantly grounded. His mentality is summed up by his famous catchphrase, \"Smesh\" representing his desire to completely destroy anyone placed in front of him.\n\nChimaev’s entry into the UFC in 2020 was nothing short of historic. He exploded onto the scene on \"Fight Island\", securing two dominant victories in two different weight classes (middleweight and welterweight) within a span of just ten days. He absorbed virtually no damage in these bouts, signaling the arrival of a generational talent. He followed this up with a chilling 17-second knockout of veteran Gerald Meerschaert, proving his power was real. While his rise was briefly stalled by a severe battle with COVID-19 that nearly forced him into retirement, he returned to face his toughest test yet against Gilbert Burns at UFC 273. In a bloody war that pushed him to his limits, Chimaev proved he had the heart and durability to match his skills, winning a unanimous decision against the elite contender.\n\nHowever, his career has also been marked by volatility, particularly regarding his weight cuts. After a massive weight miss canceled a scheduled bout with Nate Diaz, Chimaev decimated Kevin Holland in a catchweight bout without absorbing a single strike. Following this, he made the permanent move to the middleweight division. His return to the octagon at UFC 294 in October 2023 saw him face the former welterweight king, Kamaru Usman, on short notice. In a majority decision victory, Chimaev dominated the opening round with his grappling, showing that he could impose his will even against one of the greatest wrestlers in MMA history, setting the stage for a run at the 185-pound title.\n\nHis most defining statement in the middleweight division came recently at UFC 308 in October 2024, where he faced the former champion and division staple, Robert Whittaker. Many pundits expected a competitive striking battle, but Chimaev demonstrated a terrifying gap in grappling ability. In the very first round, he secured a takedown and immediately transitioned to a face crank submission that was so intense it dislocated Whittaker\'s jaw, forcing an immediate tap. This victory was a masterful display of violence that kept his undefeated record intact and catapulted him into the undisputed number one contender spot. As of 2025, Chimaev stands as the most feared man in the division, seemingly destined for UFC gold.</item>
        <item>Alexandre Pantoja is the living embodiment of the \"blue-collar champion\", a fighter whose path to glory was paved with grit, humility, and unwavering perseverance. Born in Arraial do Cabo, Brazil, on April 16, 1990, Pantoja grew up in poverty, a reality that followed him well into his professional fighting career. Unlike many athletes who find financial stability upon reaching the elite level, Pantoja famously worked as an Uber Eats driver to support his wife and children even while he was a ranked fighter in the UFC, knocking out opponents inside the octagon and delivering food on his motorbike shortly after. This backstory captured the hearts of fans worldwide, painting him as a man fighting not for fame, but for the literal survival and future of his family.\n\nInside the cage, Pantoja lives up to his terrifying nickname, \"The Cannibal.\" His fighting style is a chaotic whirlwind of aggression that rarely allows opponents a moment to breathe. He is a high-level Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu black belt with a knack for taking backs and securing submissions in scrambles, but he combines this with a brawling striking style that is reckless yet effective. Pantoja possesses an iron chin and an inhuman ability to absorb damage and keep moving forward, often dragging technically superior strikers into deep waters where his sheer will and cardio break them down. He does not point-fight; he looks to finish every exchange, making him one of the most entertaining fighters in flyweight history.\n\nHis journey to the title was a marathon, not a sprint. Pantoja first introduced himself to the UFC audience on season 24 of \"The Ultimate Fighter\", a tournament of champions where he was a standout performer. Despite his talent, he spent years as a top contender, often one win away from a title shot before stumbling. However, his resume quietly became the best in the division. He holds the unique distinction of defeating his greatest rival, Brandon Moreno, three separate times throughout their careers—once on the reality show and twice in official UFC bouts. This dominance over the division\'s biggest star proved that Pantoja was the uncrowned king long before he ever wore the gold.\n\nThe crowning moment of his life finally arrived in July 2023 at UFC 290, where he faced Brandon Moreno for the Flyweight Championship. In what was widely considered the Fight of the Year, the two rivals went to war for five grueling rounds. Pantoja, battered and bloody, refused to be denied, using his grappling and relentless pressure to secure a split-decision victory. The image of Pantoja collapsing to his knees in tears, telling his family that he could finally stop working delivery jobs and provide for them as a champion, became one of the most emotional moments in the sport\'s recent history.\n\nSince capturing the belt, Pantoja has proven to be a fighting champion, successfully defending his throne against the division\'s most dangerous challengers. He first rematched Brandon Royval at UFC 296, securing a dominant decision victory to silence any doubts about his supremacy. He then returned to his homeland of Brazil for UFC 301 in May 2024, where he defended his title against the rising Australian star Steve Erceg in a high-stakes main event. In a competitive bout that tested his wrestling and tactical intelligence, Pantoja emerged victorious once again. As the flyweight king heading into late 2025, Pantoja stands as a fortress at 125 pounds, prepared to welcome cross-promotion stars like Kai Asakura, proving that the man who once delivered food is now the undisputed ruler of the division.</item>
        <item>Alex Pereira is arguably the most terrifying and impactful combat sports athlete of his generation, a man whose rise to stardom defies all conventional logic. Born in a favela in São Bernardo do Campo, Brazil, on July 7, 1987, his early life was defined by hardship. He dropped out of school at 12 to work in a tire repair shop, where he developed an alcohol addiction that plagued his youth. Seeking a way out, he turned to kickboxing at age 21, discovering a supernatural natural power that would eventually earn him the nickname \"Poatan\", which means \"Hands of Stone\" in the indigenous Tupi language. He proudly honors his Pataxó ancestry in every walkout, entering the arena with traditional face paint and a stoic, stone-faced demeanor that strikes fear into his opponents before the first punch is even thrown.\n\nHis fighting style is a masterclass in minimalism and devastating efficiency. Pereira fights with a tall, upright stance and hands often held dangerously low, relying on his head movement and radar-like distance management to bait opponents into range. His greatest weapon is his left hook, widely considered the single most dangerous punch in combat sports history—a strike that requires very little wind-up but generates concussion-inducing force upon impact. While critics initially questioned his grappling ability given his kickboxing background, Pereira has shown remarkable anti-wrestling improvements and a calm ability to stand back up, forcing every fight to return to the standing position where he is the undisputed king.\n\nPereira’s transition to the UFC is the stuff of legend. After becoming a two-division Glory Kickboxing champion, he followed his rival Israel Adesanya to MMA. His rise was meteoric; within just a year of his debut, he challenged Adesanya for the Middleweight title at UFC 281 in Madison Square Garden. In a dramatic comeback, he knocked out the long-reigning champion in the fifth round to capture the belt. Although he lost the title in a rematch at UFC 287, the setback only propelled him to greater heights. He made the move to the Light Heavyweight division, a weight class that better suited his massive frame, and immediately began dismantling former champions.\n\nThe year 2024 solidified Pereira as the face of the company and the savior of major events. After capturing the vacant Light Heavyweight title against Jiri Procházka at UFC 295, he defended it in spectacular fashion at the historic UFC 300, knocking out Jamahal Hill in the first round with a nonchalant ease that went viral. He then stepped up on short notice to save UFC 303, destroying Procházka again with a head kick. In October 2024 at UFC 307, he showcased a different side of his game against the violent striker Khalil Rountree Jr. overcoming early adversity in a bloody war to batter Rountree into submission in round four, proving he has the durability and heart to match his power.\n\nAs of 2025, Alex Pereira stands as a global superstar and a two-division UFC champion with a resume that rivals Hall of Famers who spent a decade in the sport. He has effectively cleared out the striking threats in the 205-pound division and now faces the ultimate stylistic test against the grappler Magomed Ankalaev. Meanwhile, rumors persist of a potential move to Heavyweight to attempt an unprecedented three-division championship run. regardless of his next move, Pereira’s legacy is already secure as a real-life mythical figure who walked out of a tire shop to conquer the fighting world with stone hands and an unshakeable will.</item>
        <item>Alexander Volkanovski’s story is one of the most remarkable athletic transformations in modern sports history. Born on September 29, 1988, in Shellharbour, New South Wales, his path to fighting royalty began not on the mats, but on the rugby league field. In his early twenties, Volkanovski was a 214-pound semi-professional rugby player for the Warilla Gorillas, known for his fearlessness and ability to smash through much larger opponents as a front-rower. He famously started training mixed martial arts in 2012 initially just to stay fit during the off-season, but he quickly fell in love with the sport’s complexity. Shedding over 60 pounds to compete in the featherweight division, he carried the immense strength and durability of his rugby days into the cage, earning the nickname \"The Great.\"\n\nHis fighting style is a testament to high-level fight intelligence and tireless preparation. Training out of City Kickboxing and Freestyle Fighting Gym, Volkanovski is renowned for his mastery of range and volume. He utilizes a constant barrage of feints to freeze opponents, setting up punishing leg kicks and lightning-fast boxing combinations. Unlike many strikers, his background in wrestling (and his rugby bulk) makes him nearly impossible to hold down, granting him the freedom to dictate where the fight takes place. His cardio is legendary, often allowing him to increase his pace in the championship rounds when his adversaries are fading, breaking them with sheer output and pressure.\n\nVolkanovski’s rise in the UFC was methodical and undeniable. After tearing through the division, he dethroned long-time king Max Holloway in 2019 to capture the UFC Featherweight Championship. What followed was a reign of dominance that solidified his argument as the greatest featherweight of all time. He defeated Holloway two more times—most notably in their third bout at UFC 276, where he delivered a striking masterclass that left no doubt about his superiority. He also successfully defended his belt against dangerous finishers like Brian Ortega and \"The Korean Zombie\", escaping deep submissions and landing devastating counters to prove his resilience and well-rounded skill set.\n\nHowever, true greatness often requires risking it all, and Volkanovski’s career has been defined by his willingness to seek the hardest challenges. His ambition led him to challenge lightweight champion Islam Makhachev twice. In their first encounter, he pushed the larger champion to his absolute limit in a razor-close decision loss, earning immense respect. His subsequent short-notice rematch and a title defense loss to Ilia Topuria in early 2024 marked the first true setbacks of his title reign, signaling the end of his first chapter as champion. Critics began to question if his time at the top had passed, but Volkanovski was determined to prove that his story was far from over.\n\nThat redemption arc came to fruition in April 2025 at UFC 314. Facing the dangerous and surging contender Diego Lopes for the featherweight title, Volkanovski returned to his vintage form. He dismantled the explosive Brazilian with a tactical clinic, utilizing his superior footwork and veteran savvy to neutralize Lopes\' threats before securing a decisive victory. By reclaiming UFC gold and becoming a two-time featherweight champion, Volkanovski silenced the doubters and cemented his legacy not just as a dominant winner, but as a fighter who possesses the rare ability to rebuild and conquer again after a fall.</item>
        <item>Jack Della Maddalena has rapidly established himself as one of the most sophisticated boxers in modern mixed martial arts, carrying the hopes of Australian fans on his shoulders. Born in Perth, Western Australia, on September 10, 1996, his athletic journey began on the rugby field, a sport that instilled in him a baseline of toughness and physicality. However, at the age of fourteen, inspired by his older brother, he walked into a boxing gym and eventually transitioned to MMA. Interestingly, his professional career began disastrously with two consecutive losses, a false start that would have made many quit. Instead, Della Maddalena used these setbacks as fuel, reinventing his game to embark on a winning streak that would eventually catch the eye of the world’s premier organization.\n\nHis fighting style is a thing of beauty, often described as poetry in motion. Unlike many MMA fighters who rely on raw power or wild swinging, Della Maddalena utilizes crisp, technical boxing fundamentals that are rarely seen in the cage. He is a master of the body shot, systematically breaking opponents down by digging hooks into their ribs and liver, forcing them to lower their guard before attacking the head. He fights with a calm demeanor that borders on eerie, walking opponents down with efficient footwork and slipping punches by mere millimeters. This composure allows him to operate effectively in the pocket, delivering multi-punch combinations while remaining defensively responsible.\n\nDella Maddalena’s entry into the UFC was earned through Dana White\'s Contender Series in 2021, where he delivered a flawless performance that left the UFC President stunned. Upon officially joining the roster, he went on a tear, finishing his first four opponents in the first round. His ability to read his opponents and capitalize on openings made him look like a veteran despite his young age. Critics initially questioned his grappling defense, but he answered those doubts by displaying excellent takedown defense and the ability to scramble back to his feet, ensuring the fight remained in his domain: the striking range.\n\nThe biggest test of his career came at UFC 299 in March 2024, where he faced the durable veteran and former title challenger Gilbert Burns. For much of the fight, Della Maddalena faced adversity, dealing with Burns\' grappling and powerful counters. However, in the third round, he showcased his killer instinct. Recognizing a fleeting opening as Burns attempted a takedown, Della Maddalena launched a knee followed by a barrage of ground-and-pound elbows that secured a dramatic comeback knockout victory. This win vaulted him into the top five of the welterweight division and proved he could overcome adversity against the elite.\n\nThroughout late 2024 and 2025, Della Maddalena focused on recovering from a complex arm infection that followed the Burns fight, demonstrating patience and maturity outside the cage. His return has been highly anticipated, as he is viewed as the primary striker capable of challenging the wrestling-heavy hierarchy of the welterweight division. With his unique boxing style and finishing ability, he stands on the precipice of a title shot, aiming to become the next Australian champion following in the footsteps of Robert Whittaker and Alexander Volkanovski.</item>
        <item>Tom Aspinall represents the evolution of the heavyweight division, a fighter who moves with the speed and agility of a middleweight while possessing the knockout power of a giant. Born in Leigh, Greater Manchester, England, on April 11, 1993, Aspinall was born into a fighting family; his father was a jujitsu instructor, meaning Tom was on the mats almost before he could walk. This early immersion in martial arts gave him a grappling pedigree that is often overlooked due to his explosive striking. Unlike the plodding heavyweights of the past, Aspinall incorporates fluid footwork and head movement, a style honed through years of training boxing alongside Tyson Fury\'s family, creating a unique hybrid threat that the division had never seen before.\n\nInside the octagon, Aspinall is a finisher in the truest sense of the word. He holds one of the shortest average fight times in UFC history, rarely needing more than a single round to dispatch his opponents. His striking is lightning fast, utilizing straight punches and snapping leg kicks that catch opponents off guard. However, what makes him truly terrifying is his well-roundedness. If an opponent manages to survive the striking, Aspinall can seamlessly transition to a double-leg takedown and utilize his high-level Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu black belt skills to secure submissions. He is dangerous everywhere, creating a puzzle that few have been able to solve.\n\nAspinall\'s ascent was nearly derailed by a catastrophic knee injury just seconds into his main event fight against Curtis Blaydes in London in 2022. It was a heartbreaking moment that forced him to the sidelines for a year, leading to questions about whether he would return the same athlete. He answered those questions emphatically upon his return in July 2023, demolishing Marcin Tybura in just over a minute. He looked faster, stronger, and more mentally fortitude than ever before. This performance set the stage for a short-notice opportunity at UFC 295, where he stepped up to face the terrifying knockout artist Sergei Pavlovich for the interim heavyweight title.\n\nIn New York City, on barely two weeks\' notice, Aspinall achieved greatness. Despite facing the most dangerous puncher in the division, Aspinall stayed calm, landing two perfectly placed punches to the temple that put Pavlovich to sleep in the first round. With that victory, he became the Interim UFC Heavyweight Champion and only the third British champion in UFC history. He solidified his claim as the true king of the division at UFC 304 in Manchester, where he finally got his rematch against Curtis Blaydes. In front of a home crowd, he knocked Blaydes out in the first round, avenging his only injury-based loss.\n\nAs of 2025, Tom Aspinall finds himself in a unique position, holding the interim belt while campaigning for a unification bout against Jon Jones. While the politics of the heavyweight division have delayed the undisputed title fight, public perception has largely shifted to view Aspinall as the best heavyweight on the planet. His combination of humility outside the cage and devastating violence inside it has made him a fan favorite, and his reign sits at the center of the sport\'s most compelling narrative regarding who is truly the \"baddest man on the planet.\"</item>
        <item>Dricus Du Plessis is a force of nature who has defied conventional wisdom and technical critiques to reach the pinnacle of mixed martial arts. Born in Pretoria, South Africa, on January 14, 1994, Du Plessis was an accomplished kickboxer and judoka before transitioning to MMA. Known by his nickname \"Stillknocks\", referring to a drug causing drowsiness (implying he puts people to sleep), he carries the pride of a continent on his back. He has been vocal about his desire to be the first fighting champion to live, train, and reside in Africa, a motivation that has fueled his relentless march through the middleweight division.\n\nHis fighting style is often described as awkward, unorthodox, and chaotic, yet it is undeniably effective. Critics often point to his seemingly flat-footed movement and looping punches, but these unconventional mechanics generate immense power and create angles that confuse traditionally trained fighters. Du Plessis possesses a physical strength that is overwhelming; he bullies opponents in the clinch and ragdolls them to the mat. perhaps his greatest weapon, however, is his indomitable will and deceptive cardio. Even when he appears exhausted, breathing with his mouth wide open, he continues to press forward with high volume, often breaking his opponents mentally simply by refusing to stop attacking.\n\nDu Plessis\'s run to the title was filled with skepticism from pundits who doubted his technique would hold up against the elite. He silenced them one by one. His breakout performance came at UFC 290, where he faced former champion Robert Whittaker. Entering as a massive underdog, Du Plessis battered the legend, securing a second-round TKO that shocked the world. This victory set up a heated rivalry match against champion Sean Strickland at UFC 297 in January 2024. In a grueling five-round war, Du Plessis’s constant pressure and takedowns earned him a split decision victory, crowning him the UFC Middleweight Champion.\n\nThe legitimacy of his reign was solidified in his first title defense at UFC 305, held in Perth, Australia. Facing the two-time champion and global superstar Israel Adesanya, the buildup was intensely personal, centered around their African heritage. Inside the cage, Du Plessis proved his detractors wrong once again. Despite being out-struck at range in the early rounds, he walked through the fire, eventually dragging Adesanya to the ground in the fourth round and submitting him with a face crank. It was the first time Adesanya had ever been submitted, a feat that cemented Du Plessis\'s status as the true king of the division.\n\nHeading into late 2025, Du Plessis stands as an undefeated force in the UFC. He has cleared out the immediate threats to his throne, including two former champions, and has brought unmatched attention to MMA in Africa. While his style may never look \"pretty\" to the purists, his results are undeniable. He fights with a chaotic intensity that turns every bout into a brawl, an environment where he thrives and where, so far, no man has been able to survive against him.</item>
        <item>Max Holloway is a legendary figure in combat sports, widely recognized as one of the greatest featherweights of all time and a fan favorite for his warrior spirit. Born in Waianae, Hawaii, on December 4, 1991, Holloway embodies the \"Aloha Spirit\" combined with a fierce competitive drive. He entered the UFC at an incredibly young age, growing up in front of the fans to evolve from a raw prospect into a polished champion. Known as \"Blessed\", Holloway represents the pride of Hawaii, often carrying the flag and dedicating his fights to his community, especially in the wake of tragedies like the Maui wildfires, making him a hero far beyond the octagon.\n\nStylistically, Holloway is the premier volume striker in MMA history. He does not rely on one-punch knockout power; instead, he overwhelms opponents with a tsunami of punches, building momentum round after round until his adversaries simply wilt under the pressure. He holds numerous UFC records, including the most significant strikes landed in a career. For over a decade, he possessed a legendary chin, famously absorbing thousands of strikes without ever being knocked down, which allowed him to stay in the pocket and trade freely. His \"best boxer in the UFC\" claim is backed by his ability to mix up combinations to the head and body with endless cardio.\n\nHolloway’s career is defined by two distinct eras: his dominant reign as featherweight champion and his subsequent resilience as the number one contender. During his championship reign, he defeated legends like Jose Aldo (twice) and Brian Ortega. However, he hit a roadblock in his rivalry with Alexander Volkanovski, losing three times in highly competitive bouts. Many fighters would have faded into obscurity, but Holloway reinvented himself. He moved up to lightweight for a special BMF (Baddest Motherfucker) title fight against Justin Gaethje at UFC 300, delivering one of the greatest knockouts in history. In the literal last second of the fight, he pointed to the center of the cage, invited Gaethje to brawl, and put him out cold, creating an iconic moment that will live forever.\n\nFollowing that historic win, Holloway returned to featherweight in late 2024 to challenge the new champion, Ilia Topuria, at UFC 308. In a shocking turn of events, the invincible chin finally cracked. Topuria caught Holloway with a devastating left hook, handing the Hawaiian the first knockout loss of his storied career. It was a changing of the guard moment that signaled the end of Holloway\'s time as a featherweight title contender, but not the end of his career. The loss freed him to make a permanent move to the lightweight division, where his frame and lack of weight cutting issues make him a dangerous threat.\n\nAs of 2025, Max Holloway remains one of the biggest stars in the sport. He has transitioned fully to the 155-pound division, seeking fresh matchups and \"legacy fights\" rather than just chasing gold. His journey is a testament to longevity and the ability to entertain at the highest level. Whether he holds a belt or not, Holloway’s legacy is secure as a fighter who would fight anyone, anywhere, often giving the fans violence and heart that defines the very essence of mixed martial arts.</item>
        <item>Magomed Ankalaev is the stoic boogeyman of the light heavyweight division, a fighter whose skills are as undeniable as they are feared. Born in Dagestan, Russia, on June 2, 1992, he hails from the same rugged region that produced Khabib Nurmagomedov, though his style differs significantly from the typical Dagestani grappling mold. Ankalaev is a Master of Sport in Combat Sambo, but in the octagon, he operates primarily as a technical counter-striker. His demeanor is icy and emotionless; he rarely trash talks or engages in theatrics, preferring to let his violence speak for itself, a trait that has arguably delayed his push for superstardom despite his winning record.\n\nAnkalaev’s fighting style is a masterclass in range management and precision. He fights from both stances effortlessly, possessing a devastating front kick up the middle that he uses to manage distance and damage opponents. Unlike many light heavyweights who rely on brawling, Ankalaev is patient and calculated. However, when he chooses to grapple, his Dagestani wrestling heritage shines through; he has suffocating top control and brutal ground-and-pound. This versatility makes him a nightmare matchup, as he can out-strike the grapplers and out-wrestle the strikers, leaving opponents with no clear path to victory.\n\nHis career has been marked by a strange mix of dominance and bad luck. He famously lost his UFC debut literally in the last second of a fight he was dominating, tapping to a triangle choke with one second on the clock. Since then, he went on a massive undefeated run that led to a title fight against Jan Błachowicz at UFC 282. The fight ended in a controversial split draw, leaving the title vacant and Ankalaev frustrated with the organization. He was forced to rebuild his case, which he did with a violent vengeance. He knocked out the unpredictable Johnny Walker and continued to dismantle contenders to force his way back to the top.\n\nThe undeniable statement came at UFC 308 in Abu Dhabi in late 2024, where Ankalaev faced Aleksandar Rakić. In a high-level chess match, Ankalaev proved he was the superior mixed martial artist, utilizing his kicks and wrestling defense to secure a clear victory. This win finally cornered the UFC brass into granting him the next shot at the champion, Alex Pereira. The matchup is viewed as the classic \"striker vs. complete fighter\" dynamic, with many analysts favoring Ankalaev\'s ability to take the fight to the ground.\n\nIn 2025, Magomed Ankalaev stands as the uncrowned king in the eyes of many purists. He is widely considered the most difficult stylistic puzzle in the division. While he may lack the flamboyant personality of some of his peers, his resume is bulletproof. He represents the cold, hard reality of elite competition: a fighter who does not need to be liked to be respected, and who is on the verge of finally bringing the light heavyweight gold back to Dagestan.</item>
        <item>Belal Muhammad is the ultimate testament to the power of grinding perseverance and self-belief in the face of constant doubt. Born in Chicago, Illinois, to Palestinian parents on July 9, 1988, he proudly carries the nickname \"Remember the Name.\" For years, Muhammad was dismissed by fans and critics as a \"boring\" decision fighter or a gatekeeper. He was often the underdog, fighting in hostile territory and dealing with opponents who received more promotional push. However, he used this negativity as fuel, adopting a chip on his shoulder that drove him to train harder, eventually joining forces with Team Khabib to refine his grappling and discipline.\n\nInside the cage, Muhammad is a pressure machine. His style is not flashy, but it is drowningly effective. He utilizes a relentless pace, constantly moving forward to crowd his opponents and deny them space to operate. His boxing has improved dramatically, allowing him to throw high-volume combinations, but his true strength lies in his wrestling and clinch work. He does not look for the highlight-reel knockout; he looks to break his opponent\'s will by forcing them to work for every second of the fight. His cardio is weaponized, allowing him to maintain a frantic pace in rounds four and five when his opponents are gasping for air.\n\nHis road to the title was one of the longest in UFC history. After going unbeaten in ten consecutive fights—including wins over Gilbert Burns, Stephen Thompson, and Sean Brady—he was undeniable. Yet, he still had to wait. The narrative shifted when he finally got his rematch against champion Leon Edwards at UFC 304 in Manchester, England, in July 2024. Fighting in the champion\'s backyard at 5:00 AM local time, Muhammad put on the performance of a lifetime. He out-wrestled, slammed, and pressured Edwards for five rounds, dominating the fight to win a unanimous decision.\n\nWith that victory, Belal Muhammad made history as the first fighter of Palestinian descent to win a UFC championship. The image of him covered in confetti, holding the belt high, was a powerful moment for his community and a vindication of his years of hard work. He didn\'t just win the belt; he silenced the critics who said he couldn\'t compete at the elite level. His reign began with immediate challenges, as the welterweight division is a shark tank of grapplers and strikers, all hungry to take what he earned.\n\nLate in 2024, Muhammad faced a health setback, suffering from a severe bone infection in his foot that forced him to withdraw from a scheduled title defense against the unbeaten Shavkat Rakhmonov. Despite this, his spirit remains unbroken. As he recovers in 2025, he holds the gold and the top spot in the rankings, ready to prove once again that he is the best welterweight in the world. He has transformed from an overlooked contender into a undeniable champion who forced the world to finally Remember the Name.</item>
        <item>Arman Tsarukyan is widely regarded as the future of the lightweight division, a prodigy whose skill set is as explosive as it is technical. Born in Georgia to Armenian parents on October 11, 1996, and raising in Russia, he represents a new wave of hybrid fighters who blend the elite wrestling of the Caucasus with dynamic, modern striking. He made his UFC debut at just 22 years old on short notice against Islam Makhachev. Despite losing a competitive decision, the fight was a revelation; Tsarukyan was the first fighter to actively scramble and wrestle competitively with Makhachev, signaling to the world that a future champion had arrived.\n\nTsarukyan’s fighting style is characterized by intense athleticism and seamless transitions. He is an aggressive wrestler with a diverse array of takedowns, from single legs to body lock throws. However, unlike pure grapplers, he possesses vicious ground-and-pound and is dangerous on the feet. He throws fast, whipping kicks and spinning attacks that catch opponents off guard. His ability to scramble—to create chaos on the ground and end up in a dominant position—is perhaps the best in the division. He fights with a frantic energy that overwhelms opponents, giving them no time to set up their own game plans.\n\nAfter his debut loss, Tsarukyan went on a tear, destroying contenders and climbing the rankings. He suffered a controversial decision loss to Matej Gamrot but bounced back with a statement knockout of Beneil Dariush in late 2023. This first-round KO proved that he wasn\'t just a wrestler; he had one-shot power. This victory set up a title eliminator bout at the historic UFC 300 in April 2024 against the legendary former champion Charles Oliveira. In a fight that saw him survive deep submission attempts, Tsarukyan showed immense heart and superior top control to win a split decision.\n\nThat victory secured him the number one contender spot and a rematch with his first UFC opponent, the champion Islam Makhachev. The storyline is poetic: the young prospect who gave the champion his hardest test is returning years later, now in his prime, to finish the job. Tsarukyan has been vocal about his belief that he is the only man in the world capable of matching Makhachev\'s grappling and beating him.\n\nIn 2025, Arman Tsarukyan stands on the verge of destiny. He is young, hungry, and possesses a skill set that has no glaring holes. Whether he captures the gold or not, he has established himself as an elite fixture in the hardest division in the sport. He represents the evolution of MMA, where being a specialist is no longer enough; one must be a master of every phase of combat, and Tsarukyan fits that mold perfectly.</item>
        <item>Charles Oliveira is one of the most beloved and exciting fighters in the history of mixed martial arts, a man whose career arc reads like a movie script. Born in the favelas of Guarujá, São Paulo, Brazil, on October 17, 1989, Oliveira overcame rheumatic fever and heart murmurs as a child—conditions doctors said would prevent him from ever playing sports. He defied the odds, discovering Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu and entering the UFC at a young age. For years, he was known as a glass cannon: incredibly dangerous offensively but prone to quitting when the fight got tough. He grew up in the octagon, suffering losses, missing weight, and changing weight classes, before finally unlocking his true potential.\n\nKnown as \"Do Bronx\", Oliveira possesses the most dangerous submission game in UFC history, holding the record for most submission wins and most finishes. His style is the epitome of \"kill or be killed.\" He marches forward with Chute Boxe-style Muay Thai, knees, and elbows, with zero fear of being taken down because his guard is so lethal. If he gets knocked down, he simply invites his opponent into his guard. This fearlessness makes his fights chaotic spectacles. In his championship run, he defeated Michael Chandler, Dustin Poirier, and Justin Gaethje, often getting dropped early only to rally back and finish them, earning him a reputation for having the heart of a lion.\n\nOliveira lost his belt to Islam Makhachev in 2022, a defeat that ended his eleven-fight win streak. However, he refused to fade away. He bounced back with a dominant TKO win over Beneil Dariush, proving he was still elite. Although he lost a close split decision to Arman Tsarukyan at UFC 300, he remained a top contender. In late 2024, he engaged in a high-stakes rematch with Michael Chandler in New York, a grueling five-round battle that Oliveira won, reasserting his position at the top of the heap and proving his durability remains intact.\n\nHis resurgence led to another title opportunity, this time against the featherweight king moving up, Ilia Topuria, for the vacant lightweight strap (in a timeline where Makhachev vacated or moved up). At UFC 317 in June 2025, Oliveira faced the Spanish-Georgian phenom. Despite a valiant effort, the speed and power of Topuria proved too much, and Oliveira suffered a knockout loss. It was a heartbreaking moment for his millions of fans, but typical of Oliveira, he handled the defeat with grace.\n\nAs 2025 progresses, Charles Oliveira remains a massive superstar and a gatekeeper to the gold. He is in a unique position where he does not need a belt to sell out arenas. His legacy is already cemented as the greatest submission artist the sport has ever seen and a man who rose from the favelas to conquer the world. He continues to fight because it is who he is, always one submission away from changing the course of any fight, regardless of the opponent.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_wins">
        <item>54</item>
        <item>17</item>
        <item>27</item>
        <item>21</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>27</item>
        <item>18</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>23</item>
        <item>27</item>
        <item>21</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>22</item>
        <item>36</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_losses">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>11</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_draws">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>0</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_strike_accuracy">
        <item>89</item>
        <item>48</item>
        <item>59</item>
        <item>42</item>
        <item>61</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>62</item>
        <item>57</item>
        <item>53</item>
        <item>68</item>
        <item>49</item>
        <item>48</item>
        <item>53</item>
        <item>43</item>
        <item>49</item>
        <item>55</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_takedown_accuracy">
        <item>87</item>
        <item>61</item>
        <item>54</item>
        <item>38</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>48</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>34</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>51</item>
        <item>53</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>39</item>
        <item>37</item>
        <item>40</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_ko_wins">
        <item>49</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="fighter_sub_wins">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>13</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>22</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>